Guide to the Mattie E. Hewitt & Richard A. Smith Photograph Collection 1919-1961 (bulk 1920-1939) PR 26
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Photographic Prints
  - Marlborough Galleries, 1932 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 351)
    Broadway and 84th Street
  - Marock, Louise, 1934 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 352)
  - Marx, R., 1934 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 353)
    174 West 76th Street
  - Mason, George, Mrs., 1927 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 354)
    640 Park Avenue
  - Massa, Robert Falconer, Mrs., 1927 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 355)
    1085 Park Avenue
  - Massa, Robert Falconer, Mrs., 1932-1933 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 356)
    entral Park West, Eldorado Apartments
  - Massa, Robert Falconer, Mrs., 1934 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 357)
    The Beresford Apartments
  - Master, Arthur M., Dr., 1931 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 358)
    161 East 79th Street
  - Mattison, M. Wallace, 1930-1931 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 359)
    Lake Mahopec, NY
  - Maugham, Somerset, Mrs., 1928-1930 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 360)
    39 East 57th Street
  - Maynard, Walter E., 1922 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 361)
    114 East 40th Street
  - Mazur, Burton, 1934 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 362)
    1185 Park Avenue
  - Meighan, J. H., 1934 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 363)
    40 Fifth Avenue
  - Meigs, Averell, Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 364)
  - Melcher, H. H., 1934 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 365)
    522 East 89th Street
  - Merlo, Rose, 1934 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 366)
    13 Cornelia Street
  - Metal Products Exhibition, 1936 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 367)
    Rockefeller Center
  - Metropole Cafe, 1934 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 368)
    723 Seventh Avenue
  - Meyer, Charles, Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 369)
  - Meyer, Charles H., Mrs., 1933 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 370)
    1130 Park Avenue
  - Meyer, Theodore, 1929 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 371)
    104 East 40th Street
  - Meyers, J. E., 1945 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 372)
  - Michaelyan, Mr., 1933 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 373)
    515 Madison Avenue
  - Milburn, Francis L., 1934 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 374)
    944 Park Avenue
  - Milgrim, Sally, 1928 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 375)
    6 West 57th Street
  - Milbrook Golf Club, 1935 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 376)
  - Miller, Frances T., Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 377)
    10 East 53rd Street
  - Miller, Roswell, Mrs., 1929 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 378)
    1050 Park Avenue
  - Milne, Duncan Grinnell, Capt., 1926 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 379)
    55 East 52nd Street
  - Milne, George C. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 816)
  - Mindlin, Betty, 1936 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 380)
    Fulton Tower Apartments, East Orange, NJ
  - Mintz, Jack (Offsite-box 38, Folder 817)
  - Mittelman, J., 1934 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 381)
    215 West 179th Street
  - Mixsell, H. R., 1934 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 382)
    161 East 64th Street
  - Moakley, H., 1931 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 383)
    825 Fifth Avenue
  - Model Home (Offsite-box 38, Folder 818)
  - Modernage Furniture Co., 1929 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 384)
    541 East 17th Street
  - Moffat, Frank Everest, 1932 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 385)
    115 West 16th Street
  - Moffat, R. Burnham, 1928 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 386)
    660 Park Avenue
  - Moise, Howard, 1929 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 387)
    522 East 78th Street
  - Montgomery, Paul (Offsite-box 38, Folder 819)
  - Moore, J. A., 1934 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 388)
    304 Park Avenue
  - Moore, J. H., 1930 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 389)
    Riverside, CT
  - Moore, Paul, Mrs., 1936 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 390)
  - Morden, William (Offsite-box 38, Folder 820)
  - Morehouse, Robert (Offsite-box 38, Folder 821)
    Hastings-on-Hudson, NY
  - Morgan, Anne, [1926]-1929 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 391)
    3 Sutton Place
  - Morgan, Anne, [1930] (Offsite-box 15, Folder 392)
    219 Madison Avenue
  - Morgan, Anne, 1930-1931 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 393)
    Highland Falls, NY
  - Morgan, Anne, 1937 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 394)
    Mt. Kisco, NY
    See also: Series II, Box 30, folders 701-705
  - Moroney, James J. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 822)
    Pleasantville, NY
  - Morris, Benjamin Wister, 1926 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 395)
    439 East 51st Street
  - Morris, Lewis Spencer, Mrs., 1924 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 396)
    116 East 80th Street
  - Morton, Paul, Mrs., 1934 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 397)
    1 Sutton Place South
  - Mosse, Eric, 1947 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 398)
    75 Central Park West
  - Mount Pleasant Bank (Offsite-box 38, Folder 823)
  - Mullen, Joseph, 1930 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 399)
    Ritz-Carlton Hotel
  - Muncie, Curtis H., 1934 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 400)
    Great Neck, NY
  - Mundheim, Samuel, Mrs., 1931 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 401)
    730 Park Avenue
  - Munds, Louis de L'Aigle, Mrs., 1934 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 402)
    740 Park Avenue
  - Munn, Ector, Mrs., 1929 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 403)
    17 East 90th Street
  - Mussman, Anne, decorator, 1940 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 404)
    785 Park Avenue
  - Mussman, Anne, decorator, 1941 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 405)
    823 Park Avenue
  - Nadelman, Elie (scuplture), 1933 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 406)
    See also: Series II, Box 31, folders 706-708
  - Nannaghagan Golf Club (Offsite-box 38, Folder 824)
  - Nash, Ben, 1935 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 407)
    30 Rockefeller Plaza, Rm. 1711 (office)
  - Nast, Condé, 1927 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 408)
  - National Sculpture Exhibition, 1928 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 409)
    Broadway and 156th Street
  - Naumburg, Bernard, Mrs., undated (Offsite-box 16, Folder 410)
    133 East 68th Street
  - Netter, Dr., 1943 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 411)
    150 Central Park West
  - Neulander, Joseph, 1944 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 412)
    230 Riverside Drive
  - New Motif, 1931 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 413)
    128 East 60th Street
  - New York Herald Tribune, 1941-1946 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 414)
  - New York Times Annex, [1924] (Offsite-box 16, Folder 415)
    231-239 West 43rd Street
  - Newell's Ltd., 1933 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 416)
    536 Fifth Avenue
  - Newmark, Arthur, Mrs., 1931 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 417)
    1095 Park Avenue
  - Newton, Lucy C., 1930 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 418)
    277 Park Avenue
  - Nicholas, William G. Mrs. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 825)
  - Nicoll, Henry Denton Mrs. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 826)
    "Linden", New Windsor, NY
  - Nixon, John F., 1934 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 419)
    10 East 85th Street
  - Norrie, Gordon S., 1925 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 420)
    153 East 61st Street
  - Norton, E. Hope, 1929 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 421)
  - Novotny, C.G. (Offsite-box 38, Folder 827)
  - O'Brien, Esmond, 1928 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 422)
    168 East 74th Street
  - O'Harrow, J.W. (Offsite-box 39, Folder 828)
  - O'Laughlin, Thos. A., Mrs., 1936 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 425)
    55 Central Park West
  - O'Meara, Walter A. (Offsite-box 39, Folder 829)
  - Ogarrio, R., 1934 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 423)
  - Ohrbach, N.M (Offsite-box 39, Folder 830)
    Cruger, NY
  - Ohrstrom, George L., 1930 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 424)
    400 Madison Avenue
  - Old New York Exhibition, 1926 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 426)
    Architecture League Building
    See also: Series II, Box 31, folder 709
  - Olwell, Lee, Mrs., 1928 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 427)
    113 East 79th Street
  - Oppenheimer, Elsa, 1932 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 428)
  - Orde, Henry, 1929 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 429)
    1105 Park Avenue
  - Ormsbee, Malcolm, 1942 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 430)
    Massapequa, NY
  - Pagano, Marie, undated (Offsite-box 17, Folder 431)
    145 East 49th Street
  - Page, Arthur W., [1921] (Offsite-box 17, Folder 432)
    165 East 65th Street
  - Pagenstecker, Gustav Mrs. (Offsite-box 39, Folder 831)
    Cornwall-on-Hudson, NY
  - Palm Garden Restaurant, 1928 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 433)
    Teaneck, NJ
  - Parents Magazine, undated (Offsite-box 17, Folder 434)
  - Parera, Grace Moore, 1941 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 435)
    Sandy Hook, CT
  - Parker, Morgan (Offsite-box 39, Folder 833)
    Katonah, NY
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church, 1922 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 436)
    Park Avenue and 64th Street
  - Park, Hobart J. (Offsite-box 39, Folder 832)
  - Parsons, Frank Alvah, [1921] (Offsite-box 17, Folder 437)
    512 Fifth Avenue
  - Parsons, R.B. Mrs. (Offsite-box 39, Folder 834)
  - Payson, Harvey H., 1934 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 438)
    25 East 86th Street
  - Peabody, Charles, 1929 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 439)
    Secor Road, Millwood, NY
  - Peabody, Charles, 1930 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 440)
    141 East 72nd Street
  - Peacock, Elisabeth, 1930 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 441)
    38 East 57th Street
  - Pearl, Jack, 1934 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 442)
  - Pell, S. H. P., Mrs., [1922] (Offsite-box 17, Folder 443)
    3 East 69th Street
  - "Pelbrook Hall", Pelham, NY (Offsite-box 39, Folder 835)
  - Pelton, Henry C. (Architectural model), 1926-1931 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 444)
  - Peshkin, Murray M., 1934 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 445)
    450 West End Avenue
  - Petrasch, C. S., Mrs., 1922 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 446)
    863 Park Avenue
  - Pettigrew, T. M., 1928 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 447)
    1170 Fifth Avenue
  - Phipps, Henry, Mrs., undated (Offsite-box 17, Folder 448)
    Fifth Avenue and 87th Street
  - Pickwick Arms, 1930-1934 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 449)
    230 East 51st Street
  - Pictorial Review Co., 1927-1928 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 450)
    222 West 39th Street
  - Pinney, Claude C., Mrs., 1920 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 451)
    208 East 62nd Street
  - Place, Herman G. (Offsite-box 39, Folder 836)
  - Pope, Gene, Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 452)
  - Porter, Seton, Mrs., 1929 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 453)
    666 Park Avenue
    See also: Series II, Box 32, fodler 710-711
  - Post, George B., Mrs., [1921] (Offsite-box 17, Folder 454)
    Bernardsville, NJ
  - Postley, Sterling, Mrs., 1931 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 455)
    420 Park Avenue
  - Powelson, W. V. N., Mrs., 1932 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 456)
  - Pratt, H. I., 1924 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 457)
    26 Broadway
  - Pratt, Herbert Lee, 1925 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 458)
    1027 Fifth Avenue
  - Princeton Club, 1937 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 459)
    39 East 39th Street
  - Prizer, Mary C. (Offsite-box 39, Folder 837)
  - Proctor & Co. (Tapestry), 1923 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 460)
  - Proctor, F.F. (Offsite-box 39, Folder 838)
  - Pryibil, Paul, Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 461)
    25 East 69th Street
  - Quick, Douglas, Dr., 1931 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 462)
  - Quinby, C.B. (Offsite-box 39, Folder 839)
  - Quinn (Offsite-box 39, Folder 840)
  - Rawson, C. Gilmore, 1931 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 463)
    14 Sutton Place
  - Redmond, Roland, Mrs. (), 1925 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 464)
  - Reed, J.H. Dr. (Offsite-box 39, Folder 841)
  - Reed, Joseph V., 1929 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 465)
    941 Park Avenue
  - Reeve, Ethel M., 1929 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 466)
    17 East 49th Street (office)
  - Reeve, Ethel M., 1930 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 467)
    277 Park Avenue (apartment)
  - Reeve, Ethel M., 1935 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 468)
    10 East 53rd Street (apartment)
  - Reich, Schrenall, 1934 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 469)
    1101 Shore Road, Brooklyn, NY
  - Reichman, Arthur F., 1931, 1934 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 470)
    1070 Park Avenue
  - Reid, Whitelaw Mrs. (Offsite-box 39, Folder 842)
    "Ophir Hall", Purchase, NY
  - Reiss, B. C>, 1934 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 471)
    955 Walton Avenue
  - Resseguil, Elmer P. (Offsite-box 39, Folder 843)
  - Richard E. Thibout, Inc., 1930 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 472)
    24 West 40th Street (Shop)
  - Richard E. Thibout, Inc. [Wallpaper], 1930-1932 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 473)
  - Richard E. Thibout, Inc., 1946 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 474)
    509 Madison Avenue (shop)
    See also: Series II, BOx 32, folder 712
  - Richards, Ira, Mrs., [1926] (Offsite-box 18, Folder 475)
  - Riverdale Club House (Offsite-box 39, Folder 844)
  - Riverside Yacht Club, 1929 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 476)
  - Robbins, William M., 1931 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 477)
  - Rockefeller, John D. (Offsite-box 39, Folder 845)
    Pocantico Hills. NY
  - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1925 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 478)
  - Rockefeller, Percy (25 Broadway), 1930 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 479)
  - Rockwood (Offsite-box 39, Folder 846)
  - Roemer, Eva C., 1934 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 480)
    331 East 233rd Street, Bronx, NY
  - Rogers, Benjamin, Mrs., 1932 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 481)
    4 Sutton Square
  - Rogers, Hubert (Offsite-box 39, Folder 847)
    "The Crosways", Scarborough, NY
  - Rogerson, Mrs., 1927 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 482)
    460 Park Avenue
  - Romer, 1930 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 483)
    1115 Fifth Avenue
  - Ronner, McKee Co., 1930 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 484)
    370 Lexington Avenue
  - Roosevelt Hotel, 1946 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 485)
    Madison Avenue and 45th Street
    See also: Series II, Box 32, folders 713-714
  - Roosevelt Memorial House, 1923 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 486)
    28 East 20th Street
  - Root, C.F. III (Offsite-box 39, Folder 848)
  - Rosen, Felix T., 1921 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 487)
    157 East 70th Street
  - Rosenberg, Murray, Mrs., 1932 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 488)
  - Rosenfeld, Ernst, Mrs., 1927 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 489)
  - Ross Country Club and Health Farm, 1945 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 490)
    Monroe, NY
    See also: Series II, Box 32, folder 715
  - Ross, Walter, Mrs., 1934 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 491)
  - Rowland, Richard A. (Offsite-box 39, Folder 849)
  - Rubicam, Raymond Mrs. (Offsite-box 39, Folder 850)
  - Rubinoff, 1941 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 492)
    Hotel Essex
  - Ruby Foo Restaurant, 1945 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 493)
    240 West 52nd Street
    See also: Series II, Box 33, folder 716
  - Rupprecht, F. K., 1930 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 494)
  - Rushmore, Mrs., 1922 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 495)
    120 East 40th Street
  - Rushmore, E., Miss, 1925 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 496)
    151 East 51st Street
  - Rushmore, George, Mrs., 1925 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 497)
    151 East First Street
  - Russell, F. R., 1934 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 498)
    47 East 88th Street
  - Rutgers, Nicholas, Jr., Mrs., 1929 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 499)
  - Ruxton, A. C., Mrs., 1931 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 500)
  - Ryan, Thomas F., undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 501)
    858 Fifth Avenue
  - St. John Everett, Mrs., 1937 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 502)
    100 Myrtle Avenue, Westport, CT
  - St. Mark's Hospital, undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 503)
  - Saltus, Rollis S. (Offsite-box 39, Folder 851)
  - Saportas, Martin B., Mrs., 1928-1930 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 504)
    812 Park Avenue
  - Schacter, Hyman, 1934 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 505)
    144 West 86th STreet
  - Schaefer, Bertha, 1928 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 506)
    37 East 57th Street
  - Scheafer, Lesley G., Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 507)
    45 East 66th Street
  - Schelling, Ernest, 1931 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 508)
  - Schiffer, J.W. (Offsite-box 39, Folder 852)
  - Schinasi, Leo, 1934 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 509)
    346 West 89th Street
  - Schlesinger, Claire, 1948 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 510)
    300 East 57th Street
  - Schmidt, Mott, architect, 1923 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 511)
    Sutton Place
  - Schmidt, R. J., 1931 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 512)
    221 East 64th Street
  - Schofield, Marie Kelly, 1933 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 513)
    49 East 86th Street
  - Schroeder, E. A., Mrs., 1920 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 514)
    172 East 64th Street
  - Schroeder, E. A., Mrs., 1923 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 515)
    246 East 49th Street
  - Schullinger (Offsite-box 39, Folder 853)
  - Sea Cove Restaurant, 1942 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 516)
    208 West 72nd Street
  - Sea Fare Restaurant, 1942 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 517)
    41 West 8th Street
  - Seeley, 1930 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 518)
    Bridgeport, CT
  - Senzille, 1949 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 519)
    945 Fifth Avenue
  - Seybel, Daniel Edward (Offsite-box 39, Folder 854)
    "Hillandale", Port Chester, NY
  - Seymour Hotel, 1930 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 520)
    50 West 45th Street
  - Seymour, Stewart, 1926 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 521)
    31 West 12th Street
  - Shaffer, H., 1934 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 522)
    957 Walton Avenue
  - Shepard, Finley T. Mrs. (Offsite-box 40, Folder 855)
    Tarrytown, NY
  - Sheppard, Eugenia, 1941 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 523)
  - Sheppard, John R., 1930 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 524)
    1021 Park Avenue
  - Sherry-Netherland Hotel, 1932 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 525)
    781 Fifth Avenue
  - Shields, Cornelius Mrs. (Offsite-box 40, Folder 856)
  - Shirley, W. T., 1946 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 5261)
    See also: Box 33, folder 718
  - Shrady (Offsite-box 40, Folder 857)
  - Sicard, Charles L. (Offsite-box 40, Folder 858)
  - Sicard, G.G. (Offsite-box 40, Folder 859)
  - Siegel, Annette, undated (Offsite-box 20, Folder 527)
    See also: Series II, Box 33, folders 719-721
  - Silberseld, Eli, 1934 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 528)
    166 East 96th Street
  - Simmons Co., 1935 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 529)
  - Singer, 1949 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 530)
    216 East 49th Street
  - Skillman (Offsite-box 40, Folder 860)
  - Skipper, The, 1943 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 531)
  - Skipper, The, 1944 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 532)
    59 West 47th Street, Wentworth Hotel
  - Skipper, The, 1945 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 533)
    7 East 44th Street
    See also: Series II, Box 34, folders 722-724
  - Slade, Prescott, Mrs., 1925 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 534)
    630 Park Avenue
  - Slocum, T. W., 1922 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 535)
    19 West 44th Street
  - Smith, C. R. & W., undated (Offsite-box 20, Folder 536)
  - Smith, Homer, Mrs., 1933 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 537)
    25 East End Avenue
  - Smith, Richard A. (Offsite-box 40, Folder 861)
    Flushing, NY
  - Smith, Schuyler, Mrs., 1929 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 538)
  - Smyth, Miriam, 1925 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 539)
    155 East 49th Street
  - Snyder, Helen M., 1930 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 540)
    11 East 57th Street
  - Societé Des Couturiers de Paris (Copy photography), 1929 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 541)
  - Sondheim, Walter S., 1934 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 542)
  - Sparag, Miss, 1934 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 543)
    40 West 86th Street
  - Spencer, Vivien, 1930 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 544)
    3 East 77th Street
  - Spingarn, J.E. Mrs. (Offsite-box 40, Folder 862)
    "Troutbeck", Armenia, NY
  - Splint, Miss, 1930 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 545)
    230 East 50th Street
  - Springs, Richard A., 1934 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 546)
    853 Seventh Avenue
  - Spry, Constance, 1941 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 547)
  - Spur Office, 1931 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 548)
  - St. John's Church (Offsite-box 40, Folder 864)
  - Starosselsky, Winifred, 1931 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 549)
    215 East 73rd Street
  - Statler, Mrs., 1934 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 550)
    Pennsylvania Hotel
  - Steiner, Milton S. (Offsite-box 40, Folder 863)
  - Steisel, Jacob L., Mrs., 1942 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 551)
    1212 Fifth Avenue
  - Stenzi, Walter, 1934 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 552)
    424 East 52nd Street
  - Sterling, Olive James, 1934 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 553)
    65 East 55th Street
  - Stern Brothers, 1933 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 554)
    West 42nd Street
  - Stern, Dewitt, Mrs., 1934 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 555)
    30 Beekman Place
  - Sterner, F., [1922] (Offsite-box 20, Folder 556)
    150 East 62nd Street
  - Stevens, G. E., 1929 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 557)
  - Stiehl Furniture, 1934 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 558)
    28 West 20th Street
  - Stone, Samuel, Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 559)
  - Stout, H. H., 1929 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 560)
    Mountain Avenue, Ardsley, NY
  - Straus, Jesse, Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 561)
  - Straus, Roger W., 1935 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 562)
    6 East 93rd Street
  - Strausky, 1929 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 563)
    6 West 77th Street
  - Stryker, Lloyd P., Mrs., 1934 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 564)
    50 East 72nd Street
  - Sturtevant, George, 1931 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 565)
  - Sulgrave, 1945 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 566)
    Park Avenue and 67th Street
    See also: Series II, Box 34, folder 725
  - Sulzberger, Leo, 1932 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 567)
    150 West 79th Street
  - Sulzberger, Leo, 1937 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 568)
    1045 Park Avenue
  - Swedish Wallpaper Co., 1936 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 569)
  - Symington, A., Mrs., 1931 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 570)
    1150 Fifth Avenue
  - Talmey, Georgia, 1931 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 571)
    8 East 66th Street
  - Tavern-on-the-Green, 1950 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 572)
    Central Park West and 67th Street
  - Taylor, Harry C., undated (Offsite-box 21, Folder 573)
    43 West 9th Street
  - Taylor, Lucy, 1928 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 574)
    Decorator's Club Exhibition
  - Teller, Jane, 1923 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 575)
    419-421 East 61st Street
  - Teller, Jane, 1923 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 576)
    Southampton, NY
  - Teller, Jane, 1923 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 577)
    [Antiques]
  - Ten Park Avenue Hotel, 1938 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 578)
    10 Park Avenue
  - Thiesing, T. H., 1930 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 579)
    322 East 57th Street
  - Thomas, Andrew (Offsite-box 40, Folder 865)
  - Thomas, F. R., Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 580)
    1 Gracie Square
  - Thomas, James R., Mrs., [1929] (Offsite-box 21, Folder 581)
    135 East 19th Street
  - Thomas, Leonard, Mrs., 1924 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 582)
  - Thompson & Churchill, undated (Offsite-box 21, Folder 583)
    Lexington Avenue and 36th Street
  - Thompson, Charles H., 1934 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 584)
    148 East 53rd Street
  - Thompson, Charles H., 1936 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 585)
    315 East 51st Street
  - Thorn, J. C., 1930 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 586)
    2 East 55th Street, St. Regis Hotel
  - Thorne, Oakleigh, [1923] (Offsite-box 21, Folder 587)
    783 Park Avenue
  - Thorne, Oakleigh, [1923] (Offsite-box 21, Folder 588)
  - Thorne, Oakleigh Mrs. (Offsite-box 40, Folder 866)
  - Thorne, W. V. S., 1927 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 589)
    810 Fifth Avenue
  - Thorpe, Norah, Miss, 1931 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 590)
    434 East 52nd Street
  - Thurn, L., Mme., 1928 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 591)
    15 East 62nd Street
  - Tiffany, Belmont, Mrs., 1923 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 592)
    185 Madison Avenue
  - Tilden, John H. (Offsite-box 40, Folder 867)
    Garrison, NY
  - Tirrell House (Offsite-box 40, Folder 868)
  - Tobey Furniture Co., undated (Offsite-box 21, Folder 593)
  - Tobin, P.E. (Offsite-box 40, Folder 869)
  - Toerge, Norman, Mrs., 1926 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 594)
    821 Madison Avenue
  - Tomlinson, John C., 1927 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 595)
    15 East 92nd Street
  - Torrance, Kenneth, Mrs., 1925 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 596)
    27 East 62nd Street
  - Torrance, Kenneth, Mrs., 1928 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 597)
  - Torrey, G. Mrs (Offsite-box 40, Folder 870)
  - Town & Country Restaurant, 1943 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 598)
    284 Park Avenue
    See also: Series II, Box 34, folder 726
  - Town Hall, undated (Offsite-box 21, Folder 599)
    West 43rd Street
  - Town Hall Club, 1925 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 600)
    123 West 43rd Street
  - Town House Restaurant, 1943 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 601)
    18 East 38th Street
  - Towne, John Henry, Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 602)
    101 East 72nd Street
  - Townsend, Reginald T., 1930 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 603)
    205 East 68th Street
  - Townsend, Reginald T., 1931 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 604)
    East Norwich, NY
  - Tucker, Carl, Mrs., 1930 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 605)
    733 Park Avenue
  - Tully, Chas J. (Offsite-box 40, Folder 871)
  - Turncraft Curtains Inc., 1925-1926 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 606)
    1329 St. Nicholas Avenue
  - Tuscany Hotel, 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 607)
    120 East 39th Street
  - Tyssoski, John, 1930 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 608)
    Columbia Road, Dobbs Ferry, NY
  - Untermeyer, Samuel (Offsite-box 40, Folder 872)